{"pageProps":{"quiz":[{"id":480,"question":"Which of the following attribute triggers event when an element gets user Input?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Ondata","answer_b":"Onloadeddata","answer_c":"Oninput","answer_d":"Onhaschange","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":647,"question":"Which command can be used to count characters in a text file?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"ccount","answer_b":"fsize","answer_c":"count","answer_d":"wc","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":460,"question":"Which of the following is for title of the modal?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Modal-title","answer_b":"Modal-sm","answer_c":"Modal-lg","answer_d":"Modal-open","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":178,"question":"Which command is used to build a Docker image?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"docker built username/repository_name:1.0.1","answer_b":"docker image -t create username/repository_name:1.0.1","answer_c":"docker build -t username/repository_name:1.0.1","answer_d":"docker create username/repository_name:1.0.1","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":257,"question":"Which CMS powers around 35% of all websites on the internet?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"WordPress","answer_b":"Dropal","answer_c":"Joomla","answer_d":"Laravel","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":331,"question":"What is the best advantage of InnoDB over MyISAM?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"InnoDB is thread safe","answer_b":"InnoDB provides a transaction safe environment","answer_c":"InnoDB can handle table with more than 1000 columns","answer_d":"InnoDB provides FULLTEXT indexes","answer_e":"None of the above","answer_f":"All of the above"},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":907,"question":"This volume type can be used to share contents within containers in a pod, but will not persist beyond the life of a pod.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"EmptyDir","answer_b":"Local","answer_c":"ConfigMap","answer_d":"FlexVolume","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":273,"question":"Which ‘meta box’ is not hidden by default on Post and Page screens?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Featured Image is the meta box that is not hidden by default on Post and Page screens.","answer_b":"Featured Image is the child box that is hidden by default on Post and Page screens.","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":80,"question":"How do you create an array in PHP?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"$cars = \"Volvo\", \"BMW\", \"Toyota\";","answer_b":"$cars = newarray(\"Volvo\", \"BMW\", \"Toyota\");","answer_c":"$cars = array[\"Volvo\", \"BMW\", \"Toyota\"];","answer_d":"$cars = array(\"Volvo\", \"BMW\", \"Toyota\");","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_d","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":738,"question":"How to delete all pods in Kubernetes matching the awk pattern1 or pattern2?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl get nodes -n myns --no-headers=true | awk '/pattern1|pattern2/{print $1}' | xargs  kubectl delete -n myns pod","answer_b":"kubectl print pods  -n myns --no-headers=true | awk '/pattern1/2|pattern2/{print $1}' | xargs  kubectl delete -n myns pod","answer_c":"kubectl print pods  -n myns --no-headers=true | awk '/pattern1/2|pattern2/{print $1}' | xargs  kubectl remove -n myns pod","answer_d":"kubectl get pods  -n myns --no-headers=true | awk '/pattern1|pattern2/{print $1}' | xargs  kubectl delete -n myns pod","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":177,"question":"Which command is used to access a running container?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"docker exec -it container_id bash","answer_b":"docker fetch container","answer_c":"docker run container_id bash","answer_d":"docker login container_id","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":375,"question":"Once a table has been created in MySQL, its structure cannot be altered","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":394,"question":"To use MySQL on your computer, you'll need","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Perl, PHP Or Java","answer_b":"FTP And Telnet","answer_c":"Some Sort Of Client Program To Access The Databases","answer_d":"A Browser","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":985,"question":"How can you add a comment in a JavaScript?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"//This is a comment","answer_b":"'This is a comment","answer_c":"<!--This is a comment-->","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":113,"question":"What is the strpos() function used for?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Search for character within a string","answer_b":"Find the last character of a string","answer_c":"Both b and c","answer_d":"Locate position of a string’s first character","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":972,"question":"What is a Kubernetes volume?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The software within an OS that controls capacity allocation for nodes","answer_b":"A directory for the data accessible to containers in a pod","answer_c":"Layering software that puts apps into compartments for easier deployment","answer_d":"Code that enables two software programs to communicate","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":951,"question":"Which statement is true for Replica set?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Replica set is considered as a substitute to the replication controller. The prime function of replica set is to assure the number of pod replicas running.","answer_b":"Replica set is considered as the legacy replication controller. The prime function of replica set is to remove the number of pod replicas running.","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":802,"question":"How do you create a docker container from an image?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"docker run -it -d <image_name>","answer_b":"docker --run -it -d <image_name>","answer_c":"docker run it d <image_name>","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":933,"question":"What is a load balancer in Kubernetes?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"load balancer is a method for seperating service","answer_b":"load balancer is a method for exposing service","answer_c":"load balancer is a method for partitioning service","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":739,"question":"How to dump pod logs (stdout) in Kubernetes?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl log my-pod","answer_b":"kubectl pod logs my-pod","answer_c":"kubectl logs my-pod","answer_d":"kubectl pods logs my-pod","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"}]},"__N_SSG":true}